# LINDSAY WOLFGRAMM

### CONTACT

(385) 318-6372 LSAYWOLFGRAMM@GMAIL.COM

### **PROFILE**

Ambitious to learn new programming languages, methods, new technologies, and applications. I am a nontraditional student studying web development with professional experience in business, administrative, highlevel organization, and testing creative methods to produce the most efficient solutions. Passionate about being part of a company with opportunities to grow, that I can make a difference in the bottom line, and has a great work-life culture.

## SKILLS

- HTML
- CSS
- Familiar with JavaScript
- Strong Communication
- Collaboration
- e-Learning
- · Life-learner

### **EXPERIENCE**

USPS, SALT LAKE CITY, UT

DATA CONVERSION OPERATOR | DEC 2014 - PRESENT

Translating images unreadable by machine and performing hundreds of address searches, keying thousands of mail pieces daily.

- Recognized a top keyer in November 2021 for 89.45% efficiency, 2.50% 90 day error rate, and awarded parking stall.
- One of top 5 keyers in April 2020, keying volume of 69,278 mail pieces and filling 136 trucks each day.
- Lead position 6 months in plant operations over 30 mail clerks, delegating assignments, monitoring work loads and employees.

# VIVINT, LINDON, UT INVENTORY CONTROL OPERATIONS ANALYST |

MARCH 2013 - APRIL 2014

Consistently collected and monitored inventory and sales data, identified variances, developed improvements and minimize costs.

- Created new ROP's for several inventory items saving over \$30k/year and optimizing department functionality.
- Mitigated costs by providing feedback for new metrics and process improvements. Helped develop and drive input into efficient RMA process.
- Ensured proper asset disposal virtual transacting, cell unit activation/deactivation, and pick audit function using software programs Appolis and CMS.

# VIVINT, OREM, UT ORDER PROCESSING SPECIALIST |

MARCH 2012 - MARCH 2013

Filled multiple roles and provided cross-training throughout inventory supply chain. Identified demands by compiling metrics of forecasts using MTM and SalesPad.

- Recognized for going above and beyond in organization and proactiveness providing assistance where needed to technicians and team.
- Constructed original Service Coverage Map and Order Processing manual used in training company wide.

### REFERENCES

ELAINA ERICKSON USPS | (801) 499-6938

ADI EROR
TECHMOMS | EROR.ADRIENNE@GMAIL.COM

JENNIFER BAXTER
TECHMOMS | (801) 746-9446

## STRENGTHS

- Open and adoptable to changes, unexpected obstacles and outside perspectives
- Coach-ability and the desire to coach others
- Open to receive and deliver clear and useful criticism

### WEAKNESSES

- Lack of motivation if I'm not being challenged
- Work-life balance
- Overpacking

VIVINT, PROVO, UT

JR BUYER / PURCHASING | AUGUST 2010 - MARCH 2012

Actively gathered quotes for department purchase requests. Negotiated estimates to excellent terms saving money and steady flow of business to vendor. Purchase Order creation, and approval process.

- Renegotiated terms with Staples saving \$9k in a year of printed goods.
- Cost saving reducing spending through reconciliation of invoices and PO's through OnBase and Great Plains programs.
   Discovered many discrepancy, duplicate, and false accounts.
- Revised Purchase Requisition outline used with vendor.

### **EDUCATION**

SALT LAKE COMMUNITY COLLEGE

BUSINESS & COMPUTER SCIENCE | 2021 - PRESENT

- WEB DEVELOPMENT COURSE OF 6 MONTHS STARTING IN JANUARY 2022.
- JAVASCIPT DEVELOPER COURSE OF 6 MONTHS STARING IN FEBRUARY 2022.
- KEY COURSEWORK: CODING FROM SCRATCH, FRONT END FOUNDATIONS

TECHMOMS | SLCC COHORT | SPONSORED BY RIZENEXT

- SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT IN HTML/CSS, JAVASCRIPT, AND WIREFRAME CREATION.
- COMPLETION OF TECHNICAL SKILLS IN CYBER SECURITY, PRODUCT MANAGEMENT, UI/UX DESIGN, AGILE METHODOLOGY, PRODUCT DEVELOPMENT LIFECYCLE AND QUALITY ASSURANCE